{
    "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "rumahku yg indah. bercat merah muda,di depannya dibuat pagar, di dalam terdiri dari ruang tamu,ruang keluarga,2 kamar mandi,2 tempat tidur. di belakang ada taman dipenuhi bunga bunga yg sangat indah dan ayunan <br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "aku-dapt-tugas-dari-guru-binggris-ku-disusruh-membuat-cerita-sp-750",
            "question": "aku dapt tugas dari guru b.inggris ku disusruh membuat cerita \"spoof\" dari pngalaman pribadi, tapi aku bingung gimana crtanya. tlg bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kamu pasti punya kan pengalaman lucu ,,, kamu tulis aja bhs indonesianya nntik saya coba nerjemahin<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "did-he-has-a-bad-seat-203",
            "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-beda-auxilary-amp-operator-siapa-penemu-font-old-english-907",
            "question": "-Apa beda Auxilary &amp; Operator?    -Siapa penemu font Old English?\r\n -Kapan Bahasa Inggris masuk ke Indonesia?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "gaktau ee kak bntar takcarikan yha<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-teks-horatory-tentang-menanam-pohon-586",
            "question": "Buatkan teks horatory tentang menanam pohon\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Horatori : tema : argumentasi : saran<br><br>Planting a tree is one of the effort that we can do to make a better air quality. This is due to the ability of tree and its leaves in transforming carbon dioxide into oxygen. Therefore it is highly recommended to start plant a tree at least in our backyard.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-326",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Me : Mom, you are so beautiful in this night.\nMom : really? You never told me before mommy use beauty fash.\nMe : yes mom, you are A princess for daddy tonight, let tell Daddy, if Daddy shock, ask A opinion about you mom.\nMom : Ok , thankyou my sweetheart, i love you.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-pujian-responnya-tentang-memuji-keindahan-alam-me-798",
            "question": "buat kalimat pujian + responnya tentang memuji keindahan alam, memuji mother, father, granpa/ma, teacher, brother and sister, friend, best friend pet, your self",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Keindahan alam :<br>A: Wow! such a beautiful park.<br>B: Yea! i think so.<br><br>2. Teacher :<br>A: Thanks Miss jasmine! i understand it well than before.<br>B: Your welcome.<br><br>Semoga membantu :D",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Alam <br>A : Look at that beautiful lake !<br>B : Amazing<br>Mother<br>A : mom, you look pretty everytime !<br>B : thank you dear<br>Father\u00a0<br>A : Dad, you cook this ?<br>B : Yup.<br>A : waw, you can be a great chef<br>Grandpa<br>A: Grandpa, do you made this toys ?<br>B : yes, my dear<br>A : its look amazing !<br>Brother<br>A : Hey, you made this story ?<br>B: yup<br>A : Its so funny ! i love it<br>Teacher\u00a0<br>A : Sir, I never met a great teacher like you<br>B : thank you<br>friend :<br>A : Hey, you look pretty when you wear that dress<br>B : really ? thank you !<br>Best friend per<br>A : your cat is so cute.<br>B: Hahaha, yes, i know that<br>Yourself :<br>A : Hey, i look beautifull with this t-shirt !",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "boleh-minta-contoh-soal-dari-ungkapan-maksud-532",
            "question": "Boleh minta contoh soal dari ungkapan maksud?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maksud -&gt; Idea or opinion<br><br>I think the best way to be expert in mathematics is by practicing everyday.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}